Hey Gabe,
hope you're having a great Monday and you had a good weekend.
We're just about done with the discovery and
so I just wanted to take a minute to kind
of go through all of the items and
documents that we have here for you.
Kamin,
I'll be getting with you later to schedule some time.
Awesome.
So at the root of the repo,
you're going to find just like a master migration document.
That way you've kind of got all of the data
that you'll need or will need as we go through.
This is very extensive.
It goes over every repository that you have,
all the scopes,
basically everything that
was given to me by far away just to
make sure that everything's covered.
Complete breakdown of
your application stack and how that's going to be
migrated into AWS. We've also got this GitHub repo.
This is just a shallow clone in here is this
infrastructure analysis from GitHub where I just
kind of go over all the bits and bobs from heavy metal.
And then in here is a shallow clone of all
of your repos.
If you'd like,
we can get these transferred over to your GitHub.
Some of these
repos have a lot of your game assets and stuff.
So they're super big.
So I don't have all of them
in here, especially the other side mono repo.
But once we get started,
I can go ahead and get those
migrated all the way into your GitHub.
Other things you'll see in here is the Cloudflare
migration intake.
This is a complete and extensive like
migration workflow that I set up for you that
just kind of goes over literally every single
heavy metal.com or heavy metal domain that we have,
all of the objects that kind of go into this
and like what it's going to take to get that
taken care of for you.
There's also like code snippets that
I turned into actual code that was
just provided for me.
They came from far away.
There's also resources here.
This is just like
another CSV of everything that's inside of your current product.
And so with that, that'll conclude
the Cloudflare.
And then we also have AWS. So AWS has just a few things in here.
There's a pre-transfer
checklist.
We're just going to go through to make sure
that you have everything that you need before
we take that AWS account.
There's an inventory checklist script that we use to kind of intake
all of the objects inside of AWS so that when we transfer it,
we can confirm that everything made
it over.
That way,
if anything gets missed,
we can take care of that for you.
And then there's a cut
over plan from the moment that it gets cut over from
far away to it being in your hands and everything
that we'll do to kind of make sure that everything's sorted for you.
Awesome.
Well, I hope you're
having a great day.
And then the last one's just the big migration document.
Hope you're having a
great day.
Hope you're ready for the holidays and we'll talk soon.